

Jackson Lynch is an interactive person making interactive things in NYC. He is interested in working at the intersection of code, design and brand to create expressive product experiences. You can see his work at jacksonthats.me and can reach out to him at jacksonthatsme@gmail.com.

EXPERIENCE

Kickstarter

Product Designer 2014 - Present Brooklyn, NY

Worked independently and collaboratively to design and implement updated or new features for the Kickstarter core platform. Paired closely with engineers and product managers to realize specified experiences and interfaces and measure feature success. Light product management, feature planning, framing and reporting on a project basis. Helped formalize a Design Systems practice, determining and documenting new UX and UI patterns. Led research and integration of prototyping techniques into team-wide design processes.

Friends of The Web

Design Intern 2013 - 2014 Baltimore, MD

Worked with and learned from a close team of designers and designminded engineers to provide clients with intelligent web and mobile based product solutions. Responsibilities included web and product design, front-end development, and illustration. Clients included Order Up, U.S. Green Building Council, and House Industries as well as internal products.

EDUCATION

The Maryland Institute College of Art

Bachelor of Fine Arts, Graphic Design, 2010 - 2014

SKILLS

- Visual Product Design
- User Experience Design
- Front-end Development
- User Testing

- Prototyping
- Illustration
- Animation